{
  "questions": {
    "multiQuestions": [
      {
        "uuid": "",
        "question": "What are some properties of an instance type?",
        "answer": "vCPUs, Memory, Instance Storage, Network Performance",
        "wrongAnswers": [
          "fakeanswer1",
          "fakeanswer2",
          "fakeAnswer3",
          "fakeanswer4"
        ],
        "tags": [
          "EC2"
        ]
      },
      {
        "uuid": "",
        "question": "What is a Family Type?",
        "answer": "Instance Types with simlar settings are grouped into Family Types to help find the right settings for your needs",
        "wrongAnswers": [],
        "tags": [
          "EC2"
        ]
      },
      {
        "uuid": "",
        "question": "Name the different Family Types",
        "answer": "Micro Instances, General Purpose, Compute Optimized, GPU Instances, FPGA Instances, Memory Optimized, Storage Optimized",
        "wrongAnswers": [],
        "tags": [
          "EC2"
        ]
      },
      {
        "uuid": "",
        "question": "What are some Instance Purchasing Options?",
        "answer": "On-Demand Instances, Reserved Instances, Scheduled Instances, Spot Instances, On-Demand Capacity Reservations",
        "wrongAnswers": [],
        "tags": [
          "EC2"
        ]
      },
      {
        "uuid": "",
        "question": "What is a security group?",
        "answer": "An instance level firewall allowing you to restrict Ingress and Egress traffic by specifying what traffic is allowed to communicate with that instance",
        "wrongAnswers": [],
        "tags": [
          "EC2"
        ]
      },
      {
        "uuid": "",
        "question": "What are some options of a Security Group to restrict inbound and outbound communication to an EC2 instance?",
        "answer": "Source, Ports, and Protocols",
        "wrongAnswers": [],
        "tags": [
          "EC2"
        ]
      }
    ],
    "booleanQuestions": [
      {
        "uuid": "",
        "question": "If an EC2 instance is stopped, ephemoral storage is lost",
        "answer": "True",
        "tags": [
          "EC2"
        ]
      },
      {
        "uuid": "",
        "question": "If an EC2 instance is rebooted, ephemoral storage is lost",
        "answer": "False",
        "tags": [
          "EC2"
        ]
      }
    ],
    "checkboxQuestions": [
      {
        "uuid": "",
        "question": "What are some options to get an AMI (Amazon Machine Image)?",
        "answers": [
          "Create your own",
          "AWS Marketplace",
          "Community AMIs"
        ],
        "wrongAnswers": [
          "fakeAnswer1",
          "fakeAnswer2"
        ],
        "tags": [
          "EC2"
        ]
      },
      {
        "uuid": "",
        "question": "What are the different GLB types?",
        "answers": [
          "ELB",
          "NLB"
        ],
        "wrongAnswers": [
          "fakeAnswer1",
          "fakeAnswer2"
        ],
        "tags": [
          "EC2"
        ]
      },
      {
        "uuid": "",
        "question": "Test Question",
        "answers": [
          "Correct1",
          "Correct2",
          "Correct3",
          "Correct4",
          "Correct5"
        ],
        "wrongAnswers": [
          "fakeAnswer1",
          "fakeAnswer2",
          "fakeAnswer3",
          "fakeAnswer4",
          "fakeAnswer5"
        ],
        "tags": [
          "EC2"
        ]
      },
      {
        "uuid": "",
        "question": "Test Question",
        "answers": [
          "RigthAnswer1"
        ],
        "wrongAnswers": [],
        "tags": [
          "EC2"
        ]
      }
    ]
  }
}